highlandclassifieds.com 2016-05-11

# Highland Classifieds - Privacy Policy

Highland Classifieds has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: highlandclassiifeds.com. Highland Classifieds cares about the privacy of each user of its Web site ("user" or "you"), including those who trust us enough to place orders. In order to protect the privacy of its users, we have adopted the following policy: 

General Information  
When you use the Web site some basic general information is collected. This information is used to improve the Web site and make your use of the Web site as enjoyable and efficient as possible. Cookies are also used to help us determine the various services you use and the support you may need, and to help us detect and solve any problems you may have when using the Web site. 

This general information is used internally in connection with Highland Classified's business, including our personal, marketing and advertising efforts. 

* * *

Collecting Information From Children Younger than 13  
The Web site is not intended for use by those under the age of 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children younger than 13 years of age without obtaining verifiable parental consent.

* * *

Information We Collect From You  
Our site's registration process may require users to give us contact information (like name and email address) and unique identifiers (like social security number or tax identification number). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. We use it to complete and support your purchases from and use of the Web site, to comply with any requirements of law, and to respond to any questions you might have. Unique identifiers (such as email addresses) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system. For affiliate relationships, social security numbers may be used to report income to the appropriate government authorities. 

As you browse our web site, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to support your use of the Web site, to comply with any requirements of law, and to determine the commissions for our Affiliates. This data may be disclosed to third parties in aggregate only with no personally identifiable information ever being disclosed to affiliates.

* * *

Your Email Address and Communication With You  
We do not rent, sell, or otherwise disclose your email address to third parties. We do not Spam (send advertising emails or solo ads) our users. Your email address is required for many parts of our service. It is not required to browse the site and view ads. An email address is required to place a classified ad or auction, reply to an ad or auction, use the feedback system, sign up for a SearchAlert, or participate in our Affiliate program. 

We send a monthly email to all users. This monthly email will contain updates, news, and special offers, as well as information about your account. This email may contain advertising or offers from third parties and this will be indicated as such. If you do not want to receive this monthly email, you can opt-out from a link in the email as well as from your account page.

We send a weekly email with the status and performance of your ads to all users who have active ads listed on the Web site. If you do not want to receive this weekly email, you can opt-out from the summary area of your Members page.

We send SearchAlert emails to users up to once per day to those who have signed up for a SearchAlert when there is a match to the search criteria that they create. If you do not want to receive this email, you can delete your SearchAlert from the SearchAlert area of your Members page.

We send you email on a user's behalf when they reply to your ad. We strive to intercept unwanted replies to ads, but we take no responsibility for the content of any reply you get. Your contact information, including email address is not disclosed to browsers unless you expressly enter it into the ad for the public to see. We have a procedure for you to report unwanted replies to us as part of the email. Do not report any email we send you to authorities as Spam or your account privileges may be terminated.

We send regular account reminders to all users who have outstanding balances. If you do not want to receive these notices, you can pay the balance due via PayPal, Credit Card, or a check or money order in US funds sent to our place of business. This information is available in the account area of your Members page.

We send a weekly email to all affiliates with a short newsletter and statistics about their affiliate account. Affiliates can opt out of this email from the Affiliate Manager area.

We will send email to you for other legitimate purposes as part of the site operation. You will get email confirmation when you register, place an ad, reply to an ad, make a payment, use the feedback system, and for other operational reasons.

* * *

Your IP Address  
Your IP address is transmitted to each web server every time you make a request. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

* * *

Our Use of Cookies  
Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. They cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information. 

If you take out an ad on EPage Network Classifieds or become an affiliate we use temporary cookies to help format the page, and indicate what ads you can view. We also place permanent cookies to enable some of the advanced benefits, such as viewing all ads, for Gold members. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Most cookies expire after a certain time period. The most popular browsers, such as Netscape Navigator and Internet Explorer, can be set to give you the option of accepting or rejecting all cookies.

To use many of our services, your browser will need to be configured to accept cookies. Here's how to do it: In Netscape Navigator, click the Edit menu and select Preferences from the browser's drop-down menu. In the tree structure, click Advanced (Netscape 4) or Privacy & Security (Netscape 7). Under Cookies, you can select the option you feel most comfortable with that enables cookies. In Internet Explorer, click the View (older versions of Explorer) or Tools (current version) menu and select Internet Options from the drop-down menu. Click the Advanced tab, scroll to the Security heading, and select the option you feel most comfortable with that enables cookies. 

If you wish, you may set your browser to reject all cookies and still view the site. Because our system requires cookies for many processes, you may find that you are unable to place an ad or perform other tasks. 

* * *

Third Party Notice  
This site contains links to other sites. Highland Classifieds wants you to be aware that when you click on links (including advertising banners), which take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to such third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we expressly disclaim any and all liability for the actions of third parties, including without limitation actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of Personal Information by third parties. 

Highland Classifieds serves and receives ads from third party sites (our affiliates). Information not displayed in the ad (and thus not available to the general public via the Web) is not made available to these third party participants. 

Highland Classifieds uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising companies also may separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please go to:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>

* * *

Future Use  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

* * *

Site Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site.

* * *

Credit Card Security  
The Internet is a vast network of computers. Because the data passes from computer to computer, some Internet shoppers worry that unauthorized persons may intercept the data and gain access to credit card numbers, but shopping on a secure site is actually safer than handing a credit card to a waiter in a restaurant. Taking the steps below will lower the chances of interception of your credit card number: 

  * Limit your online shopping to Internet merchants, such as us, with sites equipped with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL prevents unauthorized people from intercepting your data. 
  * Use a browser that supports SSL. These browsers show a symbol in the status bar, such as a key or lock, when you are on a site that uses SSL. Most banks will cover the cost of fraud resulting from unauthorized use of your credit card or may limit your liability.

Credit card information collected is encrypted through Secure Sockets Layer before it is transmitted over the Internet. 

We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities, and may in our sole discretion disclose Personal Information or other information to satisfy any law, regulation, subpoena, or government request. We reserve the right to release Personal Information or other information about users who we believe are engaged in illegal activities or are otherwise in violation of our Terms of Use, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, if we believe in our sole discretion that such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate the Web site, or to protect the rights or property of EPage, its affiliates, or any of their officers, directors, or employees, agents, third-party content providers, suppliers, sponsors, or licensors. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities we reasonably believe in our sole discretion to be unlawful. 

* * *

Your Consent To This Policy  
By using the Highland Classified web site, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our Terms and Conditions take precedence over any conflicting Policy provision. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently.

* * *

Legal Disclaimer  
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by Indiana law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Indiana within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.

* * *

Choice/Opt-Out and Correct/Update  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying or removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

To opt-out from any further communications: 

  * You can send email to dave [at] highlandclassifieds.com
